exilez.com 2017-04-14

# Privacy Policy

* * *

Exilez website respect everyone’s right to privacy. As a publisher and content blogger I am committed to the safety of everyone privacy. While you are on my site, all information that has been marked to every readers, visitors and comment post email are all safe and private.

Log Files Safety  
Exilez web servers used log files that produce visitors internet protocol (IP) address, type of internet browser, ISP (internet service provider), referring or exit pages, date and time stamp, platform type, number of trends clicks, site or blog administer, user’s aggregate tracking movement. All visitors log files will not used to identify personal information, it will only serve as future site productivity.

E-mail Subscription  
Exilez email subscribers (powered by Feedburner) are oblique to include their name and email address as a private information that bond to the admin and subscribers. This information are strictly private and will never use in illegal or wrong activity.

Cookies  
Exilez used cookies to track visitors/users activity while you are browsing my site. It is a data that will be logged on user’s computer that shows your browsing activity list. Advertisers like Google used cookies on my site to monitor targeted advertisements based areas on user’s preferences, user’s visiting logged on my site and also to other internet sites. However, there are options either to accept or do not to cookies by editing your internet browsing settings or you can also delete all stored cookies when you finished browsing.

Visitor’s has an option to opt out cookies used by Google by optimizing your preference here [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Links  
Exilez has a link to other friendly sites that also collect personal identifiable information to the user. Exilez is not responsible to all information collected by other site that is why I recommended to all visitors/users that after leaving my site always read the privacy policy statements of every link site of mine that you will be visiting and also all other web site.

Advertisers  
Exilez is connected to some display and text link ad companies that has also the capabilities to collect cookies. All information is strictly for the ad company access only. These are the ad companies that I have work with: Google Adsense, Adbrite, Infolinks, Project Wonderful and Chitika. These ad companies has their own personal privacy policies.

Admin Contact Information  
For all your questions and concerns about Exilez privacy policy please feel free to [contact me](http://www.exilez.com/contact-team-exilez).
